CURRICULUM VITAE

• Name: Mark Kirwan

• Address: 62 Brookville Park, Drogheda, Co.Louth

• **Phone:** 083-3350079

• Email: mark.kirwan75@irishrail.ie

I'm a skilled Full Stack Developer with a wealth of diverse life and technical experience that I bring to every project.

I follow form as well as function. I know that the aesthetics of effective design combined with application speed, security and reliability combine to create a great user experience.

I work quickly and effectively in getting things built and working across the stack. I'm an excellent communicator who thrives in bright and enthusiastic teams and I'm also a self starter when working solo.

Professional Experience

larnrod Eireann 03/2008 - Present

Standing Project Executive

08/2019 - Present

Responsibilities and Duties

- > Knowledge of Rolling Stock maintenance practices and processes.
- > Experience of Rolling Stock depots operation and infrastructure required to support Rolling stock maintenance.
- > Strong interpersonal skills, ability to work with CME staff at all levels.

- > Relevant general management and project management experience.
- > Continuous improvement focus.
- Responsible for building and developing Fieldreach Scriptbuilder.
- Managed important vender for the supply of key components for the project.
 - Saved the Project funds by negotiating and researching.
- > Oversee and manage the Running Maintenance of the project.
- > Provide training to other staff members.
- > Responsible for the success of the project in the Drogheda region.
- > Regularly work and meet project deadlines.
- > Participate and partake in workshops with senior executives.

Key Project Achievements

I was part of a successful launch of important documents as part of phase one of the project. I was jointly responsible for the decision making and the deliverable of these, on time and within budget. These documents provide the Outline Solution Design. I was collaborating with consultants directly to achieve our goals.

Phase Two

Implementation, live testing and installation on the Running Maintenance for the Drogheda region. A key deliverable will be to design and build Scripts for the end user and working directly with staff to achieve this.

Fitter 03/2008 - 08/2019

Responsibilities and Duties

- > Team Leader consisting of 8 shift staff.
- Working on my initiative rebuilding 29000 engines.
- > Train and develop all staff members within the fitting team.
- > Communicating with Duty Manager directly with regard to team operations.
- Regularly meet deadlines for strict Train Timetable.
- > Cross-skilled development with the Electrical Team to meet the business needs.

Vehicle Mechanic, Co.Louth
Travelling - World Trip
Vehicle Mechanic Gearbox Center, Co.Cork

02/2007 - 03/2008 09/2006 - 02/2007 06/2003 - 09/2007

Skills

Full Stack Software Developer	Web Design	Project Management	SQL	Python
People Management	Procurement	Vender Management	Javascript	MongoDB
Heroku	HTML/CSS	Django	Microsoft Office	MySQL
NoSQL	Documentation	Leadership	UX	Jasmine
Mechanical	Electrical	AMT Scriptbuilder FDM	Technical Writing	Design & Implimentation
GIT	Github	Flask	Bootstrap	Materialize.css

Education, Certification & Training

Web Design Diploma	09/2018 - 02/2019
SQL Fundamentals, Advanced Querying	09/2019
AMT Sybex Training Module, Affinity Suite Fieldreach	09/2019
Full Stack Software Developer	02/2019 - 03/2020
Vehicle Mechanic	09/2000 - 07/2005

Hobbies & Interests

Bass guitarist of Rock Band, Football 5 aside twice a week, Drawing art, New Technology,
Movies, Harley Davidson owner weekend spin meet ups, Building apps and software as a
hobbie http//:www.github.com/Skillabill

References

On request.